question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
